here to do the easy consumption of
在这里做容易消费
micro-services presentation and
微服务演示和
Ted Tolson I've been doing software
泰德·托尔森（Ted Tolson）我一直在做软件
development for 20-plus years I work at
我工作了20多年
Kroger as a software architect I've been
克罗格（Kroger），我曾经是软件架构师
in retail chemical and music industry hi
在零售化学和音乐行业中喜
I'm Sean Sherwood like Ted I've been in
我是Sean Sherwood，就像Ted一样
the industry for a while
这个行业一段时间
prior to Kroger I've worked in
在克罗格之前，我曾在
telecommunications finance and
电信金融和
bioinformatics so who is Kroger it's the
生物信息学，那么谁是克罗格呢？
number 17 on the fortune 500 so it's a
财富500强中的第17位，因此
fairly large company it goes by a lot of
相当大的公司
names you'll see some of them up there
名称，您会在其中看到一些
if you're on the west coast you might
如果您在西海岸，您可能会
know Ralph's that's effectively Kroger
知道拉尔夫是有效的克罗格
and there's a bunch of other stats there
那里还有很多其他统计数据
the slides will get published all right
幻灯片将正确发布
so what's the point of this presentation
那么这个演讲的重点是什么
we want to make it easy to produce and
我们想使其易于生产和
consume micro services in a consistent
一致地消费微服务
way so all right
这样很好
that sounds great but how do we actually
听起来不错，但实际上我们如何
go about doing that well what we're
去做好我们所要做的
gonna do is we're gonna take the spring
要去做，我们要去春天
initialize our in forked how many people
初始化我们的分叉人数
here have used start spring dot IO
这里使用了启动Spring 点IO
alright pretty good show of hands I was
好吧，我的举手真不错
just getting some fresh stats it sounds
只是听起来有些新鲜统计
like that's currently creating about a
像这样目前正在创造一个
hundred and fifty thousand projects per
每个项目十五万个项目
month so it gets a lot of usage I think
一个月，所以我认为它的用法很多
it validates that it's a really solid
它证实这是一个非常坚实的
concept as a way to get your project
概念作为获取项目的一种方式
started so the agenda is going to be how
开始，所以议程将是如何
do we fork that and get set up then
我们可以叉起来然后进行设置吗
we're going to show how do you set up a
我们将展示如何设置
third-party dependency so that you can
第三方依赖性，以便您可以
use it how do you set up a VCS ignore
使用它如何设置VCS忽略
file and your generated stuff then we're
文件和您生成的内容，那么我们
gonna get into how to write tests for it
要去学习如何编写测试
and then how to create a micro Service
然后如何创建微服务
archetype with some customizations and
带有一些定制的原型和
time permitting we'll get into the
时间允许，我们将进入
super-secret bonus round so we'll see
超级秘密红利回合，让我们拭目以待
how that goes all right so for the live
一切如何顺利进行
code so enough with the slides yeah real
用幻灯片编码得足够多，是的，真的
quick I want to give you a bit of an
快速，我想给你一点
introduction just to make sure that if
介绍只是为了确保
you haven't used the initializer it is
您还没有使用初始化程序
your place to go to generate a spring
您去产生Spring 的地方
boot apps and it has a lot of options
启动应用程序，它有很多选择
dependencies and then you select
依赖关系，然后选择
generate
生成
and it'll download a zip file for you
并会为您下载一个zip文件
and then you can import that in your IDE
然后可以将其导入到IDE中
and continue your development so we are
并继续您的发展，所以我们
going to make sure that I've got my
确保我有我的
development environment set up so I can
建立了开发环境，因此我可以
actually start modifying this so I've
实际上开始修改它，所以我已经
got a fork of the initializer in my own
我自己有一个初始化程序的分支
personal github I've made actual
我已经成为现实的个人github
check-ins for the different steps that
签入的不同步骤
I'll follow so after the presentation
演讲结束后我会照做
will be links available to you where you
将是您可以使用的链接
can just go and look at it I also have a
可以去看看，我也有一个
document that's in a repo that's just
只是在回购中的文档
next to it that has really detailed
旁边真的很详细
instructions for how to follow along on
有关如何继续的说明
this if you want to go home and and try
如果您想回家尝试
to do it yourself
自己做
so to prove that I actually have this
为了证明我确实有这个
working real quick I'm gonna make a very
工作很快，我会做一个非常
small change to the HTML template that
对HTML模板的小改动
is behind the initializer and I have dev
在初始化程序的后面，我有开发人员
tools and live reload running so I
工具和实时重载运行，所以我
didn't have to have to reload that so
不必重新加载
I'm actually hooked up ready to develop
我实际上已经准备好发展
alright so there are the detailed
好吧，所以有详细
instructions on how to set up your
有关如何设置您的说明
development environment so we're kind of
开发环境，所以我们有点
skipping over that part but the links
跳过那部分，但链接
have all all the information on that so
拥有所有有关的信息，所以
our first scenario we have project teams
我们的第一个场景我们有项目团队
like most they have a properties file
像大多数一样，他们有一个属性文件
but they're not encrypting their values
但他们没有加密自己的价值
in the properties file and we really
在属性文件中，我们真的
want them to do that with anything
希望他们做任何事情
that's sensitive so we want to make it
那很敏感，所以我们要做到
easy for them to do the right thing and
他们容易做正确的事，
our solution for that then is going to
那么我们的解决方案就是
be to add in gossiped spring boots
被添加在八卦 spring boot
starter option to the initializer
初始化程序的启动程序选项
initializer is effectively what runs
初始化程序实际上是运行的
start spring dot IO so we're going to
启动spring dot IO，所以我们要
show you how to do that okay it's going
告诉你怎么做，好吧
to be a common use case if you're going
如果要去，将是一个常见的用例
to customize the initializer where
在哪里自定义初始化程序
you're going to want to add in
您将要添加
additional libraries I picked this
我选择的其他图书馆
third-party library because it's
第三方库，因为它是
available for everybody to actually look
可供所有人实际使用
at and use but also because it is an a
在使用，还因为它是一个
spring boot aware project that's not
Spring Boot知道的项目不是
actually underneath the spring boot
实际上在 spring boot 的下面
umbrella so you get the advantage of
雨伞，让您获得
using a third-party library and also the
使用第三方库以及
advantage of using spring boot and auto
使用Spring Boot和Auto的优势
configuration so to add a third-party
配置，以便添加第三方
dependency there is a small amount of
依赖有少量
gamal that you have to include yeah so
你必须包括在内
what he was doing there is uh there was
他在那里做的事
just a ton of Yambol describing the
只是一吨Yambol描述
Jessup library like the group ID
Jessup库之类的组ID
artifact ID that that kind of typical
那种典型的工件ID
stuff for a dependency and I'm gonna add
依赖的东西，我要添加
it right underneath the OP section so
就在OP部分的下方
this is the application memo file within
这是其中的应用程序备忘文件
the initializer code base so it's the
初始化代码库，因此
way initializer is set up it's it's
设置初始化器的方式是
super easy to add on your own custom
超级容易添加您自己的自定义
dependencies so I created a topic
依赖关系，所以我创建了一个主题
component and then with other called
组件，然后与其他调用
custom so I could put any of my custom
自定义，所以我可以放任何我的自定义
things underneath there in this case I'm
在这种情况下，我下面的东西
adding just the Jessup library
仅添加Jessup库
I put a description in and the group ID
我在其中输入了说明和组ID
and artifact ID that links to that
以及链接到该工件的工件ID
dependency I'll also add in a version
依赖关系，我还将添加一个版本
number and this is something that's not
数字，这不是
you not usually seen when you look at
当你看着你通常不见
the other descriptions within the boot
引导中的其他描述
yeah mo this is because it's not under
是的，这是因为它不在
spring boots management so that might
spring boot 管理，以便可能
have to be something that you have to
必须是你必须要做的事情
account for you can also actually
帐户也可以实际上
develop your own bomb where you could
在可能的地方开发自己的炸弹
manage these versions that is if you've
管理这些版本，如果您已经
been in women end up with a lot of third
曾经在女性中占第三
party or custom dependencies you'll
派对或自定义依赖项
probably want to look at doing that
可能想看看这样做
so I'll kick that off and look at my
所以我会开始，看看我的
copy of the initializer and when I just
初始化程序的副本，当我只是
started start typing in jessup you can
开始输入jessup即可
see now that library is available to me
现在看到图书馆对我可用
and because I add a description
并且因为我添加了描述
I can even type in like the word
我什至可以输入像
encryption and it'll show up so it will
加密，它将显示出来
actually match on on your descriptions
实际上符合您的描述
so when we talk about the easy
所以当我们谈论简单
consumption of micro services let's say
可以说微服务的消费
back in in your office you have some web
回到你的办公室，你有一些网络
service that's out there and it's kind
那里的服务很亲切
of complicated to call you might create
您可能会创建的复杂呼叫
a client library for that and then if
一个客户端库，然后如果
you just do this this one small little
你只需要这个小一点
step then you can run your own custom
然后您可以运行自己的自定义
version of start spring bio and that
版本的启动春生物和
would be an option to your teams so
将是您团队的一个选择，所以
anytime they want to call that service
每当他们想致电该服务时
they just click the button boom that
他们只是点击按钮
dependencies automatically in their
在他们的依赖自动
maven or Gradle file and they're ready
Maven或Gradle文件，他们已经准备好
to go so it generated it and real quick
去吧，它产生了它，而且很快
I'll open up the pom file and you can
我将打开pom文件，您可以
see that the dependency has now been
看到依赖现在
included so we have the Jessup library
包括在内，所以我们有Jessup库
included with our project and I actually
包含在我们的项目中，而我实际上
have a version of this running where I
在我那里运行这个版本
made a small modification to the
对
application properties I talked about it
我讨论过的应用程序属性
a little bit in the presentation itself
演示文稿本身
where I'm using the Jessup encryption to
我在使用Jessup加密的地方
store these properties and when you look
存储这些属性，当您查看时
at it now in on the envy of the actuator
现在，它令人羡慕执行器
you can actually see that
你实际上可以看到
the passwords been unencrypted I have
密码未加密
the second one there with password
第二个密码
specifically because you can see that it
特别是因为您可以看到它
actually started out spring boot will
实际开始 spring boot 会
actually do that for you if you name it
如果你给它命名的话
with the the word secret or key or
带有单词secret或key或
password or yet not secret but password
密码或不是秘密而是密码
how many people are using an actuator
有多少人正在使用执行器
here oh wow so that that's definitely
在这里，哇，那绝对是
that's a great library to include from
那是一个很棒的图书馆
spring it's like it's like you get loads
春天，就好像你有负载
of free functionality you just have to
免费功能，您只需要
drop it in your project and it gives you
把它放在你的项目中，它给你
a ton of the end points like he was
像他那样的大量终点
showing there that was the env end point
显示那里是环境的终点
but there's like I think 20 of them and
但是好像有20个
they keep adding better and better stuff
他们不断添加更好的东西
so definitely worth checking out so
所以绝对值得一看
probably in your organization you have
可能在您的组织中
libraries that you've built that you
您建立的图书馆
can't share outside with the outside
不能与外界分享
world this would be how you could make
世界，这将是你怎么做
those available to your teams to select
您的团队可以选择的那些
right from the initializer your custom
从初始化程序开始，您的自定义
version of the initializer and what's
初始化程序的版本以及什么
you know but this example I was showing
你知道，但是我展示的这个例子
has the starter concept to it so if you
具有入门概念，所以如果您
can take those libraries and wrap them
可以将这些库包装起来
with a starter and auto-config it makes
与启动器和自动配置，它使
it that much better for people to be
人们变得更好
able to use and consume that library
能够使用和使用该库
cool so next up the scenario we're going
很酷，所以接下来我们要进行的场景
to talk about is we have developers on
谈论的是我们有开发人员
teams who keep checking in like binary
像二进制一样不断检查的团队
files into source code control and we
文件进入源代码控制，我们
really don't want that so the simple
真的不想那么简单
solution is to give them an ignore file
解决方案是给他们一个忽略文件
but we want to make sure that they don't
但是我们要确保他们不会
have to do that manually time we want to
必须手动完成，我们想要
just automatically pop that into the
只是自动将其弹出
project any time they start a new
每当他们开始新项目时
project so that's we're gonna go modify
项目，所以我们要去修改
the initializer this time instead of
这次是初始化器，而不是
adding in like a maven control of
像maven一样加入
dependency we're actually going to just
依赖我们实际上只是
add in a file to the project that's
将文件添加到
created so to be fair there actually is
为了公平起见实际上是存在的
a ticket open up on the spring
春天开张票
initializer itself to do this this is
初始化程序本身就是这样做的
just one way of possibly doing that
只是这样做的一种方式
so I took advantage of a website called
所以我利用了一个叫做
get ignored IO I don't know if anybody
被忽略IO我不知道是否有人
has used this before but it saves me a
曾经使用过，但是为我节省了
lot of time you just go in and type in
很多时间，您只需要输入
types of things are part of your project
事物类型是您项目的一部分
and it'll generate a fairly complete get
它会生成一个相当完整的获取
ignore file so I'll take this and
忽略文件，所以我会采取这个
introduce it in as a template so what do
作为模板介绍它，怎么办
I mean by a template the generator
我的意思是通过模板生成器
that's underneath of the spring
那是春天的底下
initializer makes heavy use of groovy
初始化程序大量使用了Groovy
templates and so any of the types of
模板等等
things that are actually are generated
实际产生的东西
in the final zip file are probably
在最终的zip文件中
housed within this templates directory
放在此模板目录中
so real quick I'll just add a new gate
这么快，我将添加一个新的门
ignore file so yes I did have to make
忽略文件，所以是的，我不得不
one change to the git ignore that
git的一个更改忽略了
doesn't actually come from get ignore
实际上不是来自被忽略
and it actually has to do with the maven
它实际上与行家有关
wrapper jar for whatever reason that
包装罐无论出于何种原因
wasn't included so I was having some
不包括在内，所以我有一些
issues further downstream because that
在下游发布，因为
was not being checked in and it needs to
没有签入，它需要
be so in addition to happening the
是这样，除了发生
template there's one other thing that I
模板，我还有另一件事
need to modify and that's actually the
需要修改，这实际上是
generator itself
发电机本身
inside the project generator there is
在项目生成器内部有
this do generate project structure and
这确实产生了项目结构，
this is where most of the main work is
这是大部分主要工作所在
actually being done taking two templates
实际上完成了两个模板
and putting them in the directory right
并将它们放在目录中
before it gets zipped up so I'm just
在压缩之前，我只是
going to introduce this and what this is
要介绍这个，这是什么
going to do is going to take that file
要做的就是拿那个文件
that template file that I created the
我创建的模板文件
get ignore run it through a groovy
忽略通过常规运行它
template engine passing in the model
传递模型的模板引擎
that is all the attributes of things
这就是事物的全部属性
that you've selected on the on the form
您在表单上选择的
itself and then produce an a dot git
本身，然后产生一个点git
ignore file and generally this would be
忽略文件，通常这是
all you would need to do to make a
您需要做的所有事情
template work and be introduced into the
模板工作并将其引入
initializer however I found an really an
初始化器，但是我发现一个真正的
interesting edge case with the git
有趣的边缘情况
ignore itself the zip process that's
忽略自己的压缩过程
being used by bring it up actually right
被正确使用而被使用
now the main controller is using an ant
现在主控制器正在使用蚂蚁
builder to do a zip file set and the zip
生成zip文件集和zip文件的生成器
file set just conveniently decided to
文件集只是方便地决定
ignore a bunch of files that it thought
忽略一堆它认为是的文件
you would never want to include and
您永远不想包括
obviously in this case we really want it
显然，在这种情况下，我们真的想要它
to be included so quick I'll just add
这么快被包括在内，我将添加
this it was interesting to track down
这很有趣
but actually a very simple fix to it so
但实际上是一个非常简单的解决方案，因此
and what that did is just put another
而所做的只是放另一个
option on this to say don't exclude
这个选项可以说不排除
those default values
这些默认值
and really the soul talk is sort of
真正的灵魂对话是
about setting teams on the right path
关于在正确的道路上建立团队
from the start and so we'll keep
从一开始，所以我们会继续
building up what we do here the the
建立我们在这里所做的
dependency was the easiest thing to add
依赖是最容易添加的东西
now we're doing some files and the the
现在我们正在做一些文件，
archetypes are coming up shortly
原型即将出现
and then we'll build further from there
然后我们将从那里进一步建立
and I have an error so one of the things
我有一个错误，所以其中之一
we've seen is that you know we've had
我们已经看到的是，你知道我们已经
the question asked to us you know hey
这个问题问我们，你知道吗
how often we really start new projects
我们真正开始新项目的频率
are we doing it that frequently is it is
我们经常这样做吗
it worth getting in here and doing this
值得进入这里并这样做
I would say the fact that start spring
我会说春天开始的事实
do gets used 150,000 times a month says
确实每月使用15万次
that yes the getting a fast way to start
是的，快速入门
projects is worth it but we've seen that
项目是值得的，但我们已经看到了
you get all kinds of benefits when your
当您获得
teams start new projects in a consistent
团队以一致的方式开始新项目
way and I think a good example of that
方式，我认为这是一个很好的例子
is we we had a consistent maven setup
是我们有一致的Maven设置吗
that we were using for a long time and
我们使用了很长时间
Sean joined the team and he looked at
肖恩（Sean）加入了团队，他看着
that and he said oh hey why aren't you
那他说，哦，嘿，你为什么不
guys using sonar right now and because
家伙现在使用声纳，因为
all the project teams were we're doing
我们正在做的所有项目团队
things in a very consistent way we were
事情以非常一致的方式
able to very quickly set up a sonar
能够非常迅速地建立声纳
build on our continuous integration
建立在我们不断整合的基础上
server published that out and start to
服务器将其发布并开始
capture trends and our code coverage and
掌握趋势和我们的代码覆盖范围，并
things like that so I think it
这样的事情，所以我认为
highlights the power of putting teams in
强调将团队投入的力量
a consistent mode how you doing I don't
一致的模式我怎么不
know all right maybe I had misspelled it
知道没事吧，也许我拼错了
if not what I can do is I can just since
如果不是，我能做的就是
I've done most of this already I can go
我已经可以完成大部分工作了
ahead and jump forward yeah and so here
前进并向前跳，是的，所以在这里
he's going to show the each each one of
他将展示每个
these steps the dock he refers to that's
这些步骤，他指的是
all out on github so everything he's
全部放在github上，所以他的一切
copying from to do these steps is
复制以执行以下步骤是
already out there for you to take a look
已经在那里供您看看
at at the end of the presentation we
在演示的结尾，我们
have links to that and then in addition
有链接，然后另外
to that the the code the forked code is
那个代码的分叉代码是
all out and github as well and there's
全部以及github以及
branches for each one of the steps so if
每个步骤都会分支，所以如果
you get hung up on anything you could
你挂在任何可能的事上
just check out one of those branches and
只需检查那些分支之一，
get to a clean State for that particular
为了那个特定而干净
implementation so let's restart that so
实施，所以让我们重启
basically it was the exact same thing of
基本上，这是完全相同的
having a good ignore having that right
有一个很好的忽略权
in the project generator and in the main
在项目生成器和主
controller having the exclude and I
控制器具有排除和我
guess everybody noticed that it's
猜每个人都注意到
actually a spring group project which
实际上是一个春季小组项目
you would totally expect it to be so go
你完全希望它会这样
ahead and add that do the generate for
前面并添加为生成
us too
我们也是
and you can see now that I have a good
你现在可以看到我有一个很好的
ignore file so very straight pretty
忽略文件，所以非常直接漂亮
straightforward to make this happen
直接做到这一点
of course live coding but I have my
当然是现场编码，但我有我的
backup so the git ignore file is there
备份，以便git忽略文件在那里
and when your developer goes to commit
当您的开发人员提交时
their code they won't have files that
他们的代码，他们将没有文件
you don't want showing up all right so
你不想现身所以
the gig git ignore file is pretty
演出git的忽略文件很漂亮
straightforward it's a it's a static
直截了当是静态的
file right it it's got the same rules
正确的文件，它有相同的规则
every time our next scenario is that we
每当我们下一个场景是
want to generate a readme for the the
想要生成一个自述文件
project and we want to put in various
项目，我们想放入各种
information in there and that way you
那里的信息，你
know team has the details of how the
知道团队有如何
project got started and some even some
项目开始了，有些甚至有些
instructions on how to use the things
有关如何使用物品的说明
within the project and we're gonna
在项目中，我们将
leverage the the templating capability
利用模板功能
there to do that so like I had done
像我以前那样做
before create a new file and I'll use
在创建新文件之前，我将使用
the S key dot format instead of a
S键点格式，而不是
markdown
降价
I'll talk through this right here the
我会在这里通过
since it's a groovy template you can see
因为它是一个时髦的模板，您可以看到
that basically what I did is I are
基本上我所做的就是
executing groovy right within that
在其中执行常规操作
template so when this template gets
模板，因此当此模板获取时
processed and put into the directory
处理并放入目录
right before the zip process it'll have
就在压缩过程之前
that substitution and in fact I'm just
这种替代，实际上我只是
going to go ahead and do the next step
继续进行下一步
with this and show you what else can be
并告诉你还有什么可以
done yep because this model the model
是的，因为这个模型
that you've got of the options that
你有选择
you've got selected get introduced in
您已经选择了引入
through the template Oh things like the
通过模板哦，像
project name become available the
项目名称可用
description and you can even do a nurse
说明，甚至可以当护士
introspection then on the dependencies
内省然后依赖
that are available so I'm having an
可用的，所以我有一个
output the dependencies that were
输出的依赖项是
selected by the user at the time that
用户当时选择的
they did the generate and I actually
他们做了生成，而我实际上
wanted to add this extra little
想增加一点
complexity to this which was if they've
如果他们已经
selected a specific dependency it gives
选择了它赋予的特定依赖
me the option to put in maybe some extra
我可以选择增加一些选择
information in this case if they picked
在这种情况下，如果他们选择了信息
Jessup I'm just going to put in the text
杰西普，我要输入文本
that will give them a link to the
这将给他们一个链接到
library so they can get more information
库，以便他们可以获得更多信息
and since I've missed this go back and
既然我错过了，回去
put that in the yeah and obviously this
把它放在是的，显然这
is just an example of how you can use
只是如何使用的一个例子
the templates to generate something
生成东西的模板
dynamically at the time of project
在项目时动态地
generation we've kicked around some
我们已经踢了一些
different ideas of what else we might do
关于我们可能会做什么的不同想法
with it there's a Czech style project
它有一个捷克风格的项目
which everybody really loves it's good
每个人都真正喜欢的东西很好
at keeping consistent formatting of your
保持一致的格式
code so that might be another file that
代码，所以可能是另一个文件
you want to generate yeah you can think
你想产生是的，你可以想到
that there's all kinds of potential
有各种各样的潜力
files that you might want to do like a
您可能想要做的文件
docker file even yeah
码头工人文件甚至是的
so now when I pick my project and do the
所以现在当我选择项目并执行
generate so he's going through that
产生，所以他正在经历
pretty quickly but when we talk about
很快，但是当我们谈论
giving the team a project that's for
给团队一个专为
those who haven't used start spring oh
那些没用过的春天开始哦
that's that's what it's doing is it's a
那就是它正在做的是
it's taking all the base files you need
它会占用您所需的所有基本文件
to have a project started and it's a
开始一个项目，这是一个
it's just zipping those up and that's
只是将它们拉上拉链而已
what's downloading each time when he
他每次下载什么
clicks that button so now I've captured
单击该按钮，所以现在我已经捕获了
some of that key information and you
一些关键信息，你
might want other parts of this to be
可能希望其他部分
templatized depending on how you want
根据您的需要进行模板化
the readme to look so we talked about
自述文件，所以我们谈到了
that yes it's worked yeah it worked you
是的，它奏效了，是的，它奏效了
can see the dependencies that I had
可以看到我的依赖
selected you can see now that this
选择您现在可以看到，
Jessup dependency since it was selected
由于选择了Jessup依赖项
that little snippet of information is
那小段信息是
included and you can see that the time
包括在内，您可以看到时间
and date is included at the bottom I
日期包括在底部I
told him he looked a little shady so we
告诉他他看起来有点阴暗，所以我们
should put in a timestamp so people can
应该加上时间戳，以便人们可以
see that that actually ran all right
看到实际上没事
okay so all right so that was the the
好吧，那么很好，那是
readme file and you can see how to do
自述文件，您可以看到该怎么办
that it's relatively straightforward but
相对简单，但是
hey man even you've been doing all this
嘿，即使你一直在做这一切
work have you written a single test I'll
工作你写了一个测试我会
call right give me your DVD right now
马上打电话给我你的DVD
all right
好吧
well actually I think I've got something
嗯，实际上我认为我有一些东西
all right let's so as we're making these
好吧，让我们做这些
modifications clearly we want the the
修改显然我们想要
generator to work consistently for our
发电机为我们持续工作
teams so it's a good idea to test out
团队，所以进行测试是一个好主意
your customizations and yeah I even have
您的自定义内容，是的，我什至拥有
a whole step on this so as you would
就像您将在此上迈出的整个步骤
expect the project generator has a test
期望项目生成器进行测试
case or a test suite and I want to
案例或测试套件，我想
introduce
介绍
attest myself to test some of the stuff
证明自己去测试一些东西
that I've actually already modified so
我实际上已经修改过
here's really simple one where I'm going
这是我要去的非常简单的地方
to just generate it a fall web project
只是生成一个秋季网络项目
and after that project is generated as
在生成该项目之后
part of the test I'm going to verify
我要验证的测试的一部分
that the files actually exist as part of
这些文件实际上作为
that and I'm gonna hope for a green bar
那我希望有一个绿色的酒吧
one little side note here we're just
一个小注意事项，我们只是
throwing this straight into the the file
将此直接扔到文件中
that's Arne there or the test class
那是Arne那里或测试班
that's probably not a best practice
这可能不是最佳实践
there's frequent changes to the
的变化频繁
initializer and it's it's constantly
初始化器，它是不断的
getting new and great functionality so
获得新的强大功能
really you should try and put all your
真的，你应该尝试把你所有的
enhancements into like separate files as
增强成单独的文件
much as possible it'll make it easier to
尽可能使它更容易
take the the newer versions of
采取较新的版本
initializer as you go that's uh that's
初始化程序，随便吧
something we learned kind of the hard
我们从困难中学到了一些东西
way so I'm going to do something maybe a
这样，我将要做某事
little bit more advanced you notice then
你会注意到一点高级
when I selected the Jessup library the
当我选择Jessup库时
readme actually would be a little
自述文件实际上会有点
different than if it wasn't selected so
与未选择的情况不同
I want to verify with a custom assertion
我想使用自定义断言进行验证
there's actually a bunch of custom
实际上有一堆习惯
assertions that are already built into
已经内置的断言
this project to cert so I'll paste in
这个要认证的项目，所以我要粘贴
this code that I wrote and what it's
我写的这段代码及其含义
going to do is it's going to say does a
将要做的是说
file exist yes and if it does it has the
文件是否存在，如果存在，
content that you've expressed so now I
您表达的内容，所以现在我
can write a test case which is going to
可以写一个测试用例
be a little bit more complicated but it
有点复杂，但是
will verify then that that has produced
将验证然后产生了
the output as expected
预期的输出
so this is setting up the project with a
所以这是用
specific dependency and adding a couple
具体的依赖关系，并添加一对
of dependency groups to it and then
对它的依赖组，然后
doing this create project request then
然后执行此创建项目请求
the output of that will be tested with
的输出将与
these assertions and so here's my my new
这些断言，所以这是我的新
assertion that I just created that will
我刚刚创建的断言
say I expect that he's the the special
说我希望他是特别的
asciidoc format with the word Jessup in
单词Jessup中的asciidoc格式
it so now when I run that test case
现在，当我运行该测试用例时
assuming all goes well I should see a
假设一切顺利，我应该看到
green bar yes sweet I get to keep my
绿条，是的，甜美的
card all right so that's how you do the
卡好吧，这就是你的方式
you know test now to kind of the title
你知道现在测试标题吗
the talk the micro-service archetype we
谈论我们的微服务原型
we have teams a bunch of different teams
我们有很多不同的团队
that are creating micro services we want
正在创建我们想要的微服务
to make sure that they create them in a
确保他们在一个
consistent way there are certain best
一致的方式有一定的最佳
practices that we really want to bake
我们真的要烤的做法
into the projects that are generated so
进入生成的项目
actuator would be one example of a best
执行器将是最好的一个例子
practice it's a really nice feature to
练习这是一个非常好的功能
have in your project so we want all
在您的项目中，所以我们想要所有
projects to do that so in order to do
项目这样做是为了
that we're going to modify the
我们将要修改
initializer to have a archetype concept
初始化器具有原型概念
or basically a whole bunch of libraries
或基本上一堆图书馆
that get included automatically okay you
会自动包含在内，好吗
probably notice that I've had to type in
可能会注意到我必须输入
like web an actuator a couple times and
像将执行器连网几次
I'm lazy so I want to fix that so I
我很懒，所以我想解决这个问题，所以我
don't have to do that so what I'm going
不必这样做，所以我要去
to do is I'm going to modify the HTML
我要做的就是修改HTML
the home HTML and I'm going to add a
家用HTML，我将添加一个
drop-down to it that will allow me to
下拉菜单，这将使我能够
select I get the line numbers
选择我得到行号
from a list of candidates and that list
从候选人名单中
of candidates could include the
的候选人可以包括
different types of reference
不同类型的参考
architectures that you want to produce
您想要生产的建筑
from the initializer itself yeah so for
来自初始化程序本身，所以
this talk we're focused on a micro
这个演讲我们专注于微
service but you could have like a mobile
服务，但您可能需要一部手机
reference architecture and then the nice
参考架构，然后漂亮
thing about that is spring boots an
关于那件事是 spring boot
opinionated stack but they can only go
固执的堆栈，但他们只能去
so far with your own mobile reference
到目前为止，您拥有自己的移动参考
architecture you could take your
建筑，你可以把你的
company's look and feel and bake that
公司的外观和烘烤
into the reference architecture that way
以这种方式进入参考架构
when a team starts the project they can
当团队开始项目时，他们可以
really focus on the business
真正专注于业务
functionality and the look and feel that
功能和外观
they need to adhere to is already in
他们需要坚持的已经在
there right from the start because I'm a
从一开始就在那里，因为我是
good computer programmer I put in foo
我放在foo中的好计算机程序员
and bar just to have it a little exactly
和酒吧只是为了有一点点
extra on there but right now when I
那里有多余的东西，但是现在当我
select it nothing's actually happening
选择它实际上没有发生任何事情
well obviously I have to put some
好吧，显然我必须放一些
behavior behind that so there's actually
背后的行为，所以实际上
a JavaScript file that I need to add
我需要添加的JavaScript文件
some behavior to so if I follow along
如果我跟随一些行为
with my presentation and include this
与我的演讲，并包括这个
I'll start seeing behavior so the what
我将开始看到行为，那么
if this is really going to do is just
如果这真的要做的只是
check for the on change event and
检查变更事件，并
depending on what you selected it's
取决于您选择的是
going to check the individual starters
要检查单个启动器
that I want to be part of that one and
我想成为那个人的一部分，
in this case I am up with my rest when I
在这种情况下，当我休息时
picked actuator and history 'kz security
选择执行器和历史'kz安全性
because I want to make sure my stuff is
因为我要确保我的东西是
secure Jessop then the sleuth library
保护Jessop，然后保护侦探库
and if you haven't seen sleuth by the
如果您还没有看到侦探
way please check it out it's a very very
方式，请检查出来，这是非常非常
cool project I also have dev tools in
很酷的项目，我也有开发工具
there that's another great one
那是另一个很棒的人
so now behavior-wise I should start
所以现在从行为角度来说，我应该开始
seeing this I left ad-hoc there too so
看到这个我也临时离开了
that you that preserves the existing
保留现有的
behavior so now when I select that all
的行为，所以现在当我选择所有
of a sudden all those things are already
突然之间所有这些事情已经
selected for me so I don't have to worry
为我选择了，所以我不必担心
about it I don't even really have to
关于它，我什至不需要
think about it I just want a micro
想一想，我只想要一个微
service and I want to make sure that
服务，我想确保
it's got all the things available to it
它拥有所有可用的东西
that I think should be required you want
我认为应该是您想要的
to share the full version with the
与共享完整版本
chapter now what's the question
本章现在有什么问题
switching the full version obviously
显然切换完整版本
those yeah yep if you open up the full
那些是的，如果你打开完整的
version you'll see that the behaviors
版本，您将看到行为
all all there go back to
所有的一切都回到
I like the simple version so I generated
我喜欢简单的版本，所以我生成了
that and just to prove that they didn't
只是为了证明他们没有
just show up on the screen but they
只是出现在屏幕上，但他们
actually oh all right all right so what
哦，好吧，好吧，那又怎样
we're gonna do now is show that we can
我们现在要做的是表明我们可以
actually take that thing we just
实际上拿走了我们只是
generated and that it is in fact the
产生的，实际上是
Micra service and the Micra service
Micra服务和Micra服务
where it has a rest endpoint we're just
它有一个休息端点，我们只是
gonna hit the rest endpoint and see some
会碰到其余端点并看到一些
JSON come back so we Barney downloaded
JSON回来了，所以我们Barney下载了
s4 yeah we've downloaded the project and
s4是的，我们已经下载了该项目，
we're just gonna go ahead and build it
我们将继续进行构建
and run it that's the other nice thing
并运行它是另一件事
about actuator you may have noticed that
关于执行器，您可能已经注意到
we didn't actually code anything for the
我们实际上并没有为
the micro service so it's really kind of
微型服务，所以真的
an empty micro service but the actuator
空的微服务，但执行器
endpoints are automatically in there so
端点会自动存在
we automatically have a like a rest
我们会自动休息一下
endpoint that we can hit and if you're
我们可以点击的端点，如果您
used to looking at spring boot logs
过去看过 spring boot 日志
you'll already see there's a few things
您已经看到有几件事
that are a little different the the
有点不同
sleuth library is already active
侦听库已处于活动状态
now if I go bring that up and hit the E
现在，如果我去提起并击中E
and V but wait I'm being blocked oh oh
和V，但是等等，我被阻止了哦
we didn't expect that no because I
我们没想到不会，因为我
enabled security now I can't hit that
现在启用了安全性
endpoint because it's now considered a
端点，因为它现在被认为是
security don't point but I do know since
安全性不重要，但我确实知道
the default behavior spring boot is to
Spring Boot的默认行为是
actually echo out that password
实际回显该密码
somewhere up here well actuator yeah
在这里的某处好执行器
oh no yeah you're right spring dude does
哦，不，你是对的，春天花花公子
it that I'm not seeing it I think I
我没看到它，我想我
might have fonts too big
字体可能太大
you can always just hit the health
你总是可以健康
endpoint yep yeah just do that okay so
终结点是的，就是这样
the info and health endpoints and
信息和健康端点
actuator are not security protected so
执行器不受安全保护，因此
we're able to just jump in and actually
我们可以直接进入
there's that I'm just seeing an
我只是看到一个
interesting behavior because I'm not
有趣的行为，因为我不是
logged in I'm only seeing the up if
登录我只会看到
you're logged in you would then see that
登录后，您会看到
like history is available and this space
就像历史一样，这个空间
is it's not getting too low so uh best
它不会变得太低所以最好
micro-service ever all right well it is
微服务一直很好
running that's that's the point
运行那就是重点
oops giving it away all right okay so
哎呀，把它送走好吧，所以
let's see well I think we're doing all
让我们好好看，我认为我们正在做所有
right on time so we can get into the
准时，所以我们可以进入
bonus round really everything we've been
奖金回合实际上我们所做的一切
focusing on so far is on the code
到目前为止，重点是代码
generation side but we want to make it
一代人，但我们想做到
easy for for teams to get going so why
团队容易上手，为什么呢？
not go ahead and initialize their
不继续初始化他们的
version control right so we know that we
版本控制正确，所以我们知道我们
want them to use version control I think
希望他们使用版本控制
everybody's in agreement with that so we
每个人都同意这一点，所以我们
can just change initializer to go ahead
可以只更改初始值设定项以继续
and initialize 10 - that's crazy
并初始化10-太疯狂了
Wow I'm not worried about it you're the
哇，我不担心你是
ones it's got a demo it yeah I think I
的有演示，是的，我想我
think I got this one I think I can do
我觉得我能做到这一点
this
这个
so I'm actually gonna jump ahead on the
所以我实际上要继续前进
steps to the step that has this included
步骤已包括在内
I'll talk through some of what I'm doing
我会讲一些我正在做的事情
reset this and this is just one example
重置它，这只是一个例子
of something you might want to do that's
您可能想要做的是
beyond just the code generation
不仅仅是代码生成
obviously whatever you are doing in your
显然，无论您在做什么
shop you might want to automate through
您可能想自动化的商店
this process I'm doing this because I'm
这个过程我正在做，因为我
introducing a new library to actually
引入一个新的图书馆
allow us to do some of the operations
允许我们做一些手术
I'm including jacott and this will allow
我包括杰科特，这将允许
me from Java to now do things like the
我从Java到现在做类似
get an it get ad get commit things that
得到它得到广告得到提交的东西
you're doing every time you're
你每次都在做
generating a project one little other
一个人一个项目
thing I'm adding into this and if you're
我要加入的东西，如果你是
a UI designer please avert your eyes I'm
用户界面设计师，请您睁开眼睛
just going to add a little checkbox to
只是要添加一个小复选框
the top that will allow us to change the
顶部将使我们能够改变
behavior of whether or not it's going to
是否要进行的行为
do this get an it and even get ignore
这样做得到它甚至被忽略
based on whether or not you check it
根据您是否检查
yeah when we put this together we didn't
是的，当我们把它们放在一起时，我们没有
know that one of the main committers on
知道主要的提交者之一
the initializer project was going to be
初始化项目将是
in the room now it feels like we're
现在在房间里，感觉就像我们
messing up his behind I'm sorry our
弄乱了他的身后，对不起我们
apologies and I think based on what you
道歉，我认为基于您
were talking about earlier that this
之前在谈论这个
might break some of the ID integration
可能会破坏某些ID集成
functionality oh yeah that's something I
功能哦，是的，这就是我
don't know if you guys have seen with
不知道你们是否见过
initializer is that you can actually use
初始化程序是您可以实际使用的
like IntelliJ to point out it to do the
像IntelliJ指出的那样
the project generation which is pretty
漂亮的项目生成
cool so we've been showing everything
很酷，所以我们一直在展示一切
through the web UI but you also have the
通过网络界面，但您也有
option through the IDE okay how did you
通过IDE的选项，好吧，你怎么了
know that all right yeah that's so we're
知道，是的，所以我们
gonna go through that again now generate
将再次经历，现在生成
my demo
我的演示
and when you go into that directory I'm
当你进入那个目录时
using oh my Z shell you can see the
使用我的Z壳，您可以看到
project has already been initialized
项目已经初始化
yeah by the fact that it shows which
是的，因为它表明了
branch is on you can see the the master
分支就可以看到主人
up there there are a few little settled
那里有一些小地方
pieces that I have documented that
我记录的那些
around just execution I think some of
围绕执行，我认为
the wrapper scripts need to be set
包装脚本需要设置
executable and it's being done by the
可执行文件，并且由
zip process which happens after you're
zip流程，发生在您之后
doing the get setup I kind of did a I
做获取设置，我有点
had to do a little bit of modification
必须做一点修改
to make sure that that happened as part
确保那是一部分
of the commit otherwise it was going to
的提交，否则它将
say that's that's that's different and
说那是不同的，
they'll be like one Delta when you would
他们会像一个三角洲
generate the file oh very good well if
如果很好的话生成文件哦
you handled that one let's let's let's
你处理了，让我们让我们
take it even a little further so that
更进一步
was all initializing get locally but why
全部初始化到本地，但是为什么
not go ahead and call out to github
不要继续打电话给github
create a brand new repo on github and
在github上创建一个全新的仓库
then send the code up in there so the
然后将代码发送到那里，这样
team can really just clone it and start
团队真的可以克隆它并开始
working on their stuff can you do that
在他们的东西上工作可以做到吗
yeah that's actually really easy I'm
是的，我真的很容易
just gonna do a git push no oh wait that
只是做一个git push不，哦，等一下
didn't that didn't work that didn't work
不，那没用，那没用
specifically because github doesn't
特别是因为github没有
actually know that I'm creating this
其实知道我在创造这个
repo and it won't let you just
回购，它不会让你
arbitrarily push a project so what I
任意推动一个项目，所以我
have to do to make that work is
必须要做的就是
introduce another library which I'll do
介绍另一个我要做的图书馆
a check out to step eight to do this
签出到第八步以执行此操作
that is a github specific library that
这是一个特定于github的库
allows the ability to create projects a
允许创建项目的能力
repos within github itself I'm hiding
我隐藏在github本身内的回购
some of my credentials in a properties
我在属性中的一些凭据
file so if you want to do this yourself
文件，所以如果您想自己做
you'll need to create that file I talked
您需要创建我刚才所说的文件
about it in this in this guide but
在本指南中对此进行了说明，但是
essentially you can see that all it's
基本上，您可以看到所有内容
doing is actually pretty simple
其实很简单
it goes out to github creates a
它出去到github创建一个
repository based on the request name and
基于请求名称和
adds the description to it
添加描述
and then once that repositories eval
然后一旦该存储库评估
available I the project should be able
该项目应该能够提供
to do a push but instead of having to go
做一个推，但不必去
to command-line I'm just going to do
到命令行，我将要做
that as part of the project itself so
作为项目本身的一部分
show initializer will do that work for
显示初始化程序将为
us that means that the team doesn't
对我们来说，这意味着团队不会
really need to understand any of this
真的需要了解这些
they can just go in and say here are the
他们可以进去说这是
dependencies I need for my project and
我的项目需要的依赖关系
yes I want version control and it'll all
是的，我想要版本控制，这一切
get set up for them automatically this
为他们自动设置
idea of working with github should
与github合作的想法应该
really extend to any repository that you
真正扩展到您所拥有的任何存储库
use internally so if you've got
在内部使用，如果您有
something that isn't github as long as
只要不是github的东西
it's got some type of REST API or at
它具有某种类型的REST API或
least some kind of tooling that you can
至少可以使用某种工具
inter interact with from within Java you
从Java内部与您进行交互
should be able to do this
应该能够做到这一点
I like being able to select that because
我喜欢能够选择它，因为
that's just saving me so much time now
那真是节省了我很多时间
it's taking up just a little bit longer
它只占用了一点时间
this time before that download occurred
这次在该下载发生之前
and if we go to my git repository
如果我们转到我的git存储库
refresh this yeah you made me nervous
刷新这是的，你让我紧张
he said it's taking a little long it's
他说要花一点时间
taking a little longer you can see now
花一点时间，你现在可以看到
that I just created that through the
我刚刚通过创建
initializer and since I've got my readme
初始化程序，因为我有自述文件
it's showing up there now github with
它现在显示在那里github与
all the selections that I had all the
我所有的所有选择
dependencies the link to Jessup Day and
依赖链接到Jessup Day和
the time and date yeah you notice that
时间和日期是的，您会注意到
that's like the actual real github
就像真实的真实github
that's a little scary for a live demo
现场演示有点吓人
because networking issues are classic
因为网络问题很经典
yeah so just a kind of a funny anecdote
是的，所以只是一种有趣的轶事
on side one of my colleagues who is a
在我的一位同事中
github fanatic he's like what the heck
github狂热的他就像什么鬼东西
are you doing as I was going through
你在做我的经历吗
some of my trial runs of this because he
我的一些试运行是因为他
could he kept seeing me create these
他能一直看到我创造这些吗
little demo projects and then I was
小演示项目，然后我
going in and deleting them so this is a
进入并删除它们，所以这是一个
it's going to show up on your feet as
它会出现在你的脚上
you do this
你做这个
hopefully you're creating these for real
希望您能真正创建这些
and not just throwing them away like I
不只是像我一样丢掉它们
am alright great so we showed that we
很好，所以我们证明了我们
could integrate with github but if we're
可以与github集成，但是如果我们
talking about our whole pipeline kind of
谈论我们的整个管道
from a CD perspective what can we do
从CD的角度来看，我们该怎么办
further on this well why don't we go
进一步在这个井上，为什么我们不去
ahead and use continuous integration
领先并使用持续集成
right we want all of our team's to be
对，我们希望我们所有的团队都成为
set up with that so why don't we set
设置好了，为什么我们不设置
them up with standard builds right from
从标准开始就可以使用它们
the start so that they don't have to go
开始，这样他们就不必走了
configure their continuous integration
配置他们的持续集成
and that'll make it really easy for them
这样对他们来说真的很容易
to do the right thing so to do that
做正确的事
we're going to use Travis CI we're gonna
我们将使用Travis CI
go modify initializer to do a very
去修改初始化器做一个非常
similar thing where it's going to call
类似的东西将在哪里打电话
out well it's going to create the the
很好，它将创建
Travis file and then call out and create
Travis文件，然后调出并创建
the project and kick it off and one of
该项目并将其启动，其中之一
the reasons picked Travis is that it had
选择特拉维斯的原因是
pretty clean integration with github and
与github和
all I had to do was introduce a Travis
我所要做的就是介绍Travis
llamo file to my project interation
llamo文件到我的项目交互
steps
脚步
and I had to do really no extra work to
我真的不需要做任何额外的工作
make that happen
做到这一点
so to show you what that looks like go
为了向您展示看起来像什么
back to my presentation some additional
回到我的演讲中
information there when you're working
工作时在那里的信息
with Travis you're going to have to
与特拉维斯，你将不得不
generate an auth token kind of like your
生成类似您的身份验证令牌
github auth token since mine's already
github auth令牌，因为我的已经
available I'm just going to introduce
我将要介绍的可用
this
这个
and basically since Travis is using a
基本上是因为Travis在使用
lot of defaults all I have to tell it is
许多默认值我只需要告诉它
that this is a Java project and I want
这是一个Java项目，我想要
it to build with the Oracle JDK 8 it
它与Oracle JDK 8一起构建
will infer a lot of other of the details
会推断出很多其他细节
based on the project that I have you can
根据我拥有的项目
go in and add all those details if you
进入并添加所有这些详细信息，如果您
need to but I wanted to kind of go with
需要，但我想与
the simple as possible all right if you
简单的就可以吧
think about it each time you're starting
每次开始时都要考虑一下
a new project there's a there's a ton of
一个新的项目有很多
busy work usually you have to do at the
繁忙的工作通常必须在
start of the project of oh hey let me go
哦，让我走了
request a version control repo and let
请求版本控制存储库并让
me go request space to run my continuous
我去请求空间来连续运行
integrations and let me go set up all my
整合，让我去建立我所有的
continuous integrations my continuous
持续集成，持续不断
build any kind of like functional tests
建立任何类似的功能测试
that you have automated all that stuff
您已经自动化了所有这些东西
and really have to do all that before
真的必须做所有的事
you can start to focus on any of the
您可以开始专注于任何
business functionality so the idea here
业务功能，所以这里的想法
is that we just automate that whole
是我们只是使整个过程自动化
process and a team you know if they're
过程和一个团队，您知道他们是否
doing scrum or something can basically
做scrum之类的事情基本上可以
get everything they need before the
在获得所需的一切之前
start of the project done very very
项目的开始做得非常非常
quickly with this and then they can
快速与此，然后他们可以
focus on the business logic immediately
立即关注业务逻辑
actually I'm gonna cheat on this just in
其实我要在这方面作弊
a timeframe perspective and check out
时间表透视图并签出
that code I'll walk through it
该代码，我将遍历它
because I had to introduce another
因为我不得不介绍另一个
dependency I'm having to do refresh and
依赖，我必须刷新
rebuild on the project yeah dev tools is
在项目上重建是的，开发工具是
very nice but it can't quite do
很好，但是做不到
everything for the automatic detection
一切用于自动检测
reload
重装
jump too far
跳得太远
I added the option to basically be able
我添加了该选项，基本上可以
to turn off Travis integration if you
如果您关闭Travis集成
didn't want it and then I'm checking for
不想，然后我正在检查
that as part of the generation process
作为生成过程的一部分
Travis does not have a nice Java library
Travis没有好的Java库
like like the github did so what I had
就像github一样，我所拥有的
to do is actually just use the spring
要做的实际上只是使用Spring
rest template and make the rest calls to
休息模板并进行其余调用
Travis if you've not seen Travis before
特拉维斯（如果您以前没有看过特拉维斯）
by the way get to repository in order to
顺便说一句到仓库以
turn on behavior in Travis you have to
打开特拉维斯的行为，你必须
sync with your account and then flip a
与您的帐户同步，然后翻转
switch before Travis will start doing
在Travis开始做之前切换
continuous integration that's manual so
持续集成是手动的，因此
I'm gonna try to work around that
我将尝试解决该问题
through the REST API so here I'm getting
通过REST API，所以我在这里
my authorization together I'm verifying
我正在一起验证
myself as a user I'm doing the sync
我自己是用户，我正在同步
through the rest interface that sync is
通过其余接口，同步是
a sync is asynchronous so you kind of
同步是异步的，所以您有点
have to wait for it to be done so what
必须等待它完成，所以
will happen is the request is going
将会发生的是请求的去向
through just making sure that it's not
通过确保它不是
sinking there's actually an attribute
下沉实际上是一个属性
that Travis gives you back that tells
特拉维斯给你的回馈告诉
you whether it's syncing or not take it
您是否正在同步
off let it cook okay since it's a bit of
让它煮好吧，因为有点
a cooking show yeah
烹饪节目是的
so this one this one starts to take a
所以这一个这个开始采取一个
little bit more time because the code
因为代码多了一点时间
needs to get up there and then Travis
需要起床然后特拉维斯
organ EADS to see it in sync
器官EADS同步查看
like he was talking about so when he
就像他说的那样，当他
says baking Travis org is free so they
说烘焙Travis org是免费的，所以他们
have a limited number of servers that
服务器数量有限
they can do builds on you not always
他们可以不总是依靠你
guaranteed to get an immediate build
保证立即得到构建
that way so it may not automatically
这样，它可能不会自动
kick off so I can talk through a little
揭开序幕，让我可以讲一点
bit more of this basically again it's
再多一点，基本上是
just the rest the steps via rest to
剩下的就是休息的步骤
activate that repository I have to have
激活我必须拥有的存储库
the Travis llamo file in my project when
我的项目中的Travis llamo文件何时
I do the push for Travis now to see it
我现在为Travis进行推送以查看它
so Travis will on push see that yeah
所以特拉维斯会努力推动
yeah mo file and then go ahead and start
是的，然后开始
off start the continuous integration
开始持续整合
build and
建立和
let's see is that the one I just created
让我们看看我刚刚创建的那个
yeah
是的
I probably shouldn't pick at us
我可能不应该选我们
so you can see now the Travis is
所以你现在可以看到Travis是
actually kicking off the build
真正开始构建
I'll follow along with it so it's doing
我会跟着它做
the normal maven downloads of
正常的Maven下载
dependencies and it will kick off the
依赖关系，它将开始
maven test yeah so just to review what
专家测试是的，所以只是回顾一下
happened there he kind of zipped through
发生在那里，他有点拉链
quickly but he had selected the
很快，但他选择了
micro-service archetype and and said hey
微服务原型，并说嘿
give me a stash or give me a git repo
给我一个藏匿处或给我一个git repo
when he clicked that generate button
当他单击生成按钮时
this time instead of just giving the zip
这次不只是提供拉链
file
文件
it also initialized get it called out to
它也初始化得到它叫出来
github created a new repo check that
github创建了一个新的仓库检查
brand-new code up into the repo created
全新代码进入创建的仓库
a Travis CI file then because he's got
一个Travis CI文件，然后因为他
the syncing between Travis org and his
Travis org和他的组织之间的同步
get repo
获取回购
Travis org saw that new repo and went
Travis org看到了这个新仓库
ahead and said oh I see you want to
向前说哦，我知道你想
build I'm gonna go ahead and kick off
建立我要去开始
your build although well actually
您的构建虽然很好
technically speaking you you actually
从技术上来讲，你实际上
told it to run the build right or nope
告诉它运行构建权或否
so the the presence of Travis GML on the
因此Travis GML的存在
git push was what triggered the actual
git push触发了实际
build so the steps had to be done in
构建，因此必须在步骤中完成
just the right way I had to actually
正确的方式我不得不
make sure that I created
确保我创建了
did the sync in on Travis of the
在Travis上同步了
repository even though there was no code
仓库，即使没有代码
there trigger it to say okay build if on
在那里触发它说可以，如果在
check in of a Travis Hamel file and then
签入Travis Hamel文件，然后
do the get steps that I had this is
做我有这个的步骤
possible very easy and in this respect
在这方面可能非常容易
because it's using a configuration file
因为它正在使用配置文件
to define the build steps other tools
定义构建步骤其他工具
that might do continuous integration
可能会持续集成
might be a little harder for you to work
可能会使您工作更难
with in this respect so if you had to
在这方面，所以如果你必须
work with a REST API to be able to
使用REST API能够
create a template and set up your build
创建一个模板并设置您的构建
steps it's going to be a little bit more
步骤将要多一点
work that's why I kind of like this
这就是为什么我喜欢这样的工作
approach of having a build pipeline file
具有构建管道文件的方法
defined within the project itself it's
在项目本身中定义的
part of the project
项目的一部分
you know what's changed as if anybody's
你知道发生了什么变化，好像有人
changed that the build behavior this
改变了这个的构建行为
would this approach would actually work
这种方法会切实有效吗
with things like
像这样
concore CI or get lab very easily this
重击CI或很容易得到实验室
would just transfer to those individual
只会转移给那些人
CI CDD tools and as I said it can
CI CDD工具，正如我所说的那样
actually take it a little while because
实际上要花一点时间，因为
it's free that's a free service but in
是免费的，是免费的服务，但是在
this case we did actually get the build
这种情况下我们确实得到了构建
was successful out there so everything
是成功的，所以一切
worked smoothly yeah and then back to
工作顺利，然后回到
slides
滑梯
all right so we've demonstrated a bunch
好吧，我们已经展示了一堆
of integrations here there's there's
的集成这里有
even more stuff you could do we talked
您可以做的更多事情
about the ability to add docker support
关于添加Docker支持的功能
if you wanted so if your teams are
如果您愿意的话，如果您的团队是
interested in building a docker image
对构建Docker映像感兴趣
you could make that right into the build
您可以将其正确构建
process through this you could add
通过此过程，您可以添加
another application lifecycle management
另一个应用程序生命周期管理
tools like a wiki or
维基或
issue tracking or things like that and
问题跟踪或类似的事情，以及
then what you could also do to really
那你也可以做些什么
complete the full cycle is ask the team
完成整个周期是问团队
not only what dependencies they want but
他们不仅想要什么依赖关系，而且
do what do they want from an environment
做他们想从环境中做什么
perspective you know do they want a
角度，你知道他们想要一个
database do they want like a messaging
他们想要像消息一样的数据库吗
service like rabbit or things like this
像兔子这样的服务
and then you could just call out to
然后你可以打电话给
Cloud Foundry and say spin up an
Cloud Foundry并说旋转
application server a database and all
应用程序服务器数据库和所有
these things and you could also spin up
这些东西，你也可以旋转起来
their dev stage environments and that
他们的开发阶段环境
that then at that point really lets a
然后在那个时候真的让
team get started on the business
团队开始业务
functionality right away and they can be
功能马上就可以了
productive and demoing to their business
生产和演示业务
within that first sprint if you remember
如果您还记得第一次冲刺
the the presentation around the the
围绕的演示
circle of code I consider this kind of
我认为这种代码圈
like the origin of that that circle of
就像那个圆圈的起源
code is that this is how you get your
代码是，这就是您得到您的方式
code into that process of being able to
编码到能够
go through those cycles this is the the
经过那些周期，这是
origins story of your code so to speak
您的代码的起源故事可以这么说
right right yeah and for the reference
对对对，供参考
architecture as we mentioned mobile
我们提到的移动架构
would be another possible reference
将是另一个可能的参考
architecture for just like a rich web
就像富网站一样的架构
application you can have an angular
应用程序可以有一个角度
based application or react and you like
基于应用程序或做出反应，您喜欢
I said you could bake in your your
我说你可以烤你的
standard look and feel you could bake
您可以烘烤的标准外观
and your your standard monitoring
和您的标准监控
solutions that you like your teams to
您希望您的团队提供的解决方案
use all that kind of stuff
用所有这些东西
so here are the the links at the
所以这里是链接
presentation lengths when he was when
演讲时长
you were looking at all the instructions
你在看所有的指示
for that that's that's what he was
因为那就是他
looking at right there and then the code
看那里，然后代码
link that's basically the forked
基本上是分叉的链接
initializer with all the branches
具有所有分支的初始值设定项
showing really everything we demoed here
展示我们在这里演示的所有内容
today so you can take a look at that and
今天，您可以看一下
then the last link is just the general
那么最后一个链接就是一般
github project where all these repos are
所有这些仓库都是的github项目
at I know I
在我知道我
there's obviously that step missing from
很明显，这是缺少的一步
from the project that I'd started to
从我开始的项目
document I just didn't get time to
我只是没时间去做的文件
finish it but the the goal was to go
完成它，但目标是去
from Travis to push to pivotal web
从Travis推向关键网络
services and actually within Travis
服务，实际上在Travis内部
that's about five or six lines of the
大约是五六行
Travis Campbell to do that so it
特拉维斯·坎贝尔（Travis Campbell）就是这样做的
wouldn't be too hard to take what's
拿什么不会太难
there already and go ahead and see part
已经在那里，继续前进，看看一部分
of that vision I think if you then
我认为如果你那么
included the manifest along with it as
连同清单一起包括
part of the generation process you're
您是生成过程的一部分
really close to being able to to see end
真的很接近看到结束
to end from initializer to production to
从初始化器到生产结束
production and available you have to
生产和可用，您必须
prove your users to hit yeah
证明您的用户是
and we're really excited about this
我们对此感到非常兴奋
concept because not only does it get a
概念，因为它不仅获得了
team started quickly but because they're
团队起步很快，但是因为他们
a provision in a very standard way we've
以非常标准的方式提供
already seen there's there's lots of
已经看到那里有很多
additional things you can start to add
您可以开始添加的其他内容
into that so this was just kind of
因此，这只是一种
scratching the surface of what's
抓东西的表面
possible open it for questions yeah so
可能打开它来提问
are there any questions so I did it make
有什么问题，所以我做到了
sense that's alright
感觉还好
all right good it's kind of a bit much
好吧，有点多
to catch in in 50 minutes but 60 minutes
在50分钟到60分钟内赶上
okay thanks for coming
好的，谢谢你的光临
you
您